mediashakers.com 2018-05-15

# Mediashakers - Privacy Policy

**Last updated: March 23, 2016**

Thank you for visiting the [www.mediaskakers.com](http://www.mediaskakers.com/) website (the "Website"). Your privacy and the integrity of any information you provide are important to us at Mediashakers Corp. and/or its affiliates (“Company”), the operator of this website.

We are accountable for our Privacy Policy and our practices on our Website, including the Privacy Policy as set out below. If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please address them via e-mail to us via our “Contact Us” page.

This Website may be connected by "hyperlinks" to other third party sites. We are not responsible in any way for the privacy practices on other third party sites and suggest that you review the privacy policies on those linked sites before using them.

**What is Personal Information?**

Personal information is any piece of information about an identifiable individual. Personal information also includes the name, title, business address, or business telephone number of an employee of an organization (“Personal Information”).

The terms “we”, “us” and “our” means  Mediashakers Corp. and/or its affiliates or Company as designated herein, or an employee or independent contractor of the company. 

“You”, “your” and “user” means the individual who is a customer by virtue of viewing our materials or using our online services.

Company is committed to use the highest standards in data security and privacy policies. We believe that genetic information is personal and private and highly confidential. You should have total control over access to your personal information and be the only one who decides who can view or share your information.

**Privacy and Usage of User’s Personal Information**

Company will use the public or private user characteristics only to analyze and gather statistical aggregate information about the users of its Website. Such statistical analysis may include, but is not limited to: users by age, gender or any other user characteristic. User’s identities will never be revealed.

Data Disclosure: In the events of legal processes served upon Company or in situations where Company rights and and/or properties need to be defended in relation to your agreement with us and as and only when the law requires us, Company may disclose your information to the relevant authorities as required.

Except for the above, Company will under no circumstances provide any third party, access to any of your personal data, unless you grant us an explicit authorization.

**The Use of email Addresses**

Your email address will only be used for the purposes of contacting you and other users in order to fulfill the services offered by Company. This may include Company newsletters, friend’s invitations, notes about your results, etc. Email addresses will never be provided to any third party, without a written approval, or an electronic consent from you. Users can opt out from Company newsletters and from other email related activities by providing the company with a written notice (email is sufficient).

**Use or Disclosure for Marketing Purposes**

Unless you have requested not to receive any marketing materials, we may also use (but will not disclose) your personal information to promote and market additional goods, services and special offers from us, our affiliates and/or our business associates including by means of direct marketing. We may also disclose your name and mailing address to these affiliates and/or business associates so that they can send you promotional materials directly. You may withdraw consent at any time, subject to our Privacy Policy. If you wish to withdraw your consent, please contact us at <http://mediashakers.com/index.php/contact-ms>. We will inform you of the implications of withdrawing consent.

**What Information is Collected?**

We collect three kinds of information from our Website:

  1. your voluntarily provided Personal Information;
  2. anonymous information about your visit; and;
  3. "cookie" based information to help us track which pages on our Website you're most interested in.

(1) Your Personal Information:

During normal Website usage, you can visit our site without communicating any personal information. However, to make use of certain features on our site, such as personalized services, or newsletters, users may be asked to register with us.

As part of this voluntary registration, we may request contact information (such as name, mailing address, email address, etc.) and other data required for operating these services. We may only collect personal information from you if you voluntarily provide it. By voluntarily providing this personal information to us, by sending us a comment or suggestion, you will be consenting to the collection, use and distribution of your personal information by us for the purposes set out herein. You are under no obligation to provide us with personal information, and may access and enjoy many parts of our website without providing us any personal information.

Among other things, the following is a representative list of reasons we may ask for your personal information:

  * To run our promotions;
  * To respond to your questions or the comments that you email to us;
  * To provide you with newsletters or other subscription information;
  * To gather aggregate information on website use and to provide services to the public of a general or specific nature, paid or unpaid.

(2)        Anonymous Information About Your Visit:

When you visit our Website, information about your visit (e.g. how you navigate the site) may be collected and stored. This information may include the length of your visit, the date and time of your visit, the pages you look at and the sites you visit before and after leaving our site. It does not include personally identifiable information such as your name, mailing or email address or telephone number. We use this non-identifiable and aggregate information to better design our website and for the purpose of optimizing our services and/or business. We also may share this general non-identifiable information with our affiliates, suppliers, sponsors and advertisers.

(3)        "Cookie" Based Information:

To tailor our Website to the needs and interests of our visitors and users, we keep track of the pages visited by our users by placing a small entry-in text file, called a "cookie", on your hard drive. A cookie is transferred to your browser by a web server and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. Cookies do not reveal personal information. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself such as email address, purchases and preferences. Cookies cannot read data from your hard drive.

Please Note: You may visit the Website with your cookies turned off. However, you may not be able to access some of the areas of our site, which require cookies for customization and personalization.

**How does the Privacy Policy deal with Children?**

Children should always get permission from their parents before sending information about themselves (such as their names, email addresses, and phone numbers) over the Internet. We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 18 years of age. Our Website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 18 years old. We will not knowingly encourage any minor to register with our site or to access those features which require registration. If a child has provided us with personal information, we ask that any concerned parent or guardian of the child contact us to confirm his/her permission.

**What if you do not agree with our Privacy Policy?**

By visiting our Website and voluntarily providing personal information to the Website, You agree to the terms of the online Terms of Use Agreement and this Privacy Policy. However, we welcome your comments and/or suggestions on improving our website and policies. If you do not agree to these terms, or wish to limit the use of any of your personal information that we may have, You may contact us via email at our “Contact Us” page. In the case of promotions or sponsors, we will occasionally ask if You consent to the forwarding of Personal Information to our promotional, sponsors and advertising partners. You may confirm or decline your consent.

**Data storage and archival**

Company uses a hosting provider that conforms to all necessary data security and availability. Company has no intention to delete your data at anytime unless so requested by You.

Company will protect Personal Information with appropriate safeguards and security measures. Company utilizes a combination of physical, administrative and electronic measures to ensure Personal Information is adequately protected on a day-to-day basis, for storage and disposal.

Company reserves the right to add, modify or otherwise update this Privacy Policy at any time and at its sole discretion. Modification notices will not necessarily be emailed out. It is your responsibility to check for any updates from time to time as well as the updated date of this policy to review any revisions or modifications.
